# **Donnelly Earley**

Full Stack Software Developer

- Madison, Alabama
- **%** (256) 808 6461
- @ donnellyearley@gmail.com

I am a self-taught full stack Software Developer with 4+ years of experience with a passion for creating efficient and user-friendly software solutions. I am seeking a role where I can utilize my technical expertise to contribute to the development of modern applications and provide value to the organization.

## **Profiles**

in Donnelly Earley

Onnelly Earley

# **Education**

Huntsville High School August 2009 - May 2013 High School Diploma

University of Alabama in Huntsville August 2013 - Withdrawn

Major: Computer Science

#### References

# Sally Davis

Software Lead @ eTruckBiz

Phone Number: (256) 533 - 5367

## Skills

**HTML** 

**CSS** 

**JavaScript** 

Node JS

**Web Applications** 

nginx

**SQL** 

**AWS** 

Linux Windows

**API Integration** 

**HCL Volt MX** 

# Experience

## eTruckBiz

August 2019 - Present

Software Developer

Huntsville, AL

https://www.etruckbiz.com

- Develops and maintains the SaaS web application suite clients utilize to manage their fleet, track important metrics, and generate various reports.
- Supports the development of mobile applications that are a part of the SaaS suite.
- Consults with internal personnel and clients to gather feedback on current systems.
- Utilizes the latest industry trends on writing clean, efficient code.

#### DriveTime

August 2018 - March 2019

Dealership Coordinator

Huntsville, AL

- Ensured vehicle titles were properly filled out and transferred to customers.
- Maintained the cleanliness and organization of the lot.
- Provided light auto-repair when needed.
- Swapped cars from one lot to another without incurring damages.

## Marco's Pizza

May 2015 - March 2018

Manager

Madison, AL

- Provided excellent customer service by taking orders by phone and in person.
- Ensured customer satisfaction by handling complaints in a respectful and timely manner.
- Was responsible for all phases of food preparation, cooking, and delivering the correct order to customers.
- Assisted with managing store inventory by counting and ordering food, drink, and produce orders.
- Was responsible for opening and closing duties including drawer counts and delivering nightly deposits to the bank.
- Was proficient with all aspects of the POS system.

#### Volunteering

### **Autism Resource Foundation**

Present

Event Helper

Huntsville, AL

https://www.theautismresourcefoundation.org/

Helps with setup of various events to promote the awareness for autism.